Adidas has been on a bit of a hot streak
when it comes to lifestyle sneakers and
this sneaker might be a big part of that
conversation. This is the Adidas Adistar
Jellyfish by Pharrell Williams. It's a
shoe that actually released last year,
but has been getting a lot more love
this year. Uh for those that don't know
much about this shoe, it's a lifestyle
silhouette that's basically an exploded
version of the Adistar Control 3. Some
of the details include AdiPRENE here for
the mid-sole. We have the torsion plate
that runs through the shoe and it comes
over on the medial side and the lateral
side, but the biggest feature is these
exploded [music]
fins. You can see here how it has fins
here. It has fins for the three stripes.
It's like these rubber overlays on top
of the shoe [music] that almost feel
like jellyfish tentacles that stretch
out from the shoe. It gives the shoe a
very base-age aerodynamic sort of look.
You can see the air just kind of flowing
over these or jellyfish. You can see the
water just kind of flowing over these.
Now, the price point for these is $300
and this pair in particular is called
the crystal sand colorway. These
released already over on Pharrell's
website, so the numbers have been
limited, but there's going to be a wider
release this week. So, if you're
interested in getting yourself a pair,
here is a closer look at the shoe and
some of the details. It is definitely
something more on the lifestyle side and
something that I've seen a lot of people
talk about online that they want to get
themselves a pair. So, if Pharrell and
Adidas and the Adistar Jellyfish are on
your list, look for these to drop later
this week.